Subtitledtrailers.com
A woman vanished last night.
We just found the body.
Prints?
And the head...
is missing.
He calls himself The Snowman killer.
He's completely insane.
I'm thinking that he is going off
to women that he disapproves of.
The only thing we know for sure
is that he is playing games with us.
We need a way to lure him out.
Be careful.
We don't know
what we are dealing with.
He's been watching us
the whole time.
Building snowmen,
cutting things up into small pieces.
He is taunting us.
If we don't find him,
this is never going to stop.
Come on!
Another missing woman.
There's something we're not seeing.
What matters most is that we celebrate
the way this is brought us together.
Anyone can see
that he is trying to hide something.
You can't force the pieces to fit.
You could have saved them.
No.
I gave you all the clues.